How to use Qlou202.4.1
From Qlou202.4.1 update, we optimized the function structure of Qlou202.4.1.
We can implement a more flexible Qlou202.4.1.
Through this video, let's learn in detail how to use Qlou202.4.1.
In this version, we have improved the main menu structure.
Therefore, the position of Qlou202.4.1 has also changed.
You can click on the production in the top menu.
Select Qlou202.4.1 in the drop-down menu to start using this function.
We can click on the plus sign in the upper right corner on the left.
Add a new Qlou202.4.1.
This is the same as the previous Qlou202.4.1.
Under the setting of this add mode, you can change the color and texture.
In addition, in Qlou202.4.1, we can also set the Qlou202.4.1.
The different material properties, such as the physical properties of the fabric, the shape of the button, and the line are applied in different Qlou202.4.1.
This function allows you to freely create more types of Qlou202.4.1.
Click on the add button in the default setting on the right side.
You will see the window to add Qlou202.4.1.
In this window, you can check the materials used in the currently selected Qlou202.4.1.
Such as fabric, fabric, stickers, etc.
And the software will display according to the material type classification.
You can define the settings and options of each module according to your own needs.
Then add a new Qlou202.4.1.
Next, let's take a look at the Qlou202.4.1.
Let's take a look at each option in the window.
Let's see how to use them in different scenarios.
We can use the button in the upper right corner.
Unify the materials that have been classified.
You can also select the button on the right side of each material.
Do a separate setting.
We can stop the mouse on the icon in the upper right corner.
Check the material, all properties and link settings.
If you want to know more about the content.
You can also click on the handbook at the bottom.
Check the official website for instructions.
Click on the add button at the bottom of the window.
You will add a flag according to the current setting.
Every time you click on the add button, you can add a flag.
Click on the add and close button.
It will add a flag according to your settings.
And close the current window.
If you need to add another flag.
When you open the window again.
All options will become default options.
All will be set as material options.
Please remember this in your work.
In order to better show the difference between options.
I will name the created flag as material.
Next, we will change the main fabric texture of the baseball.
Here we only changed the material module information.
Similarly, we can also adjust the property editor.
Its material type and color.
Click on the update button.
You can see the zoom effect after the update.
Next, let's talk about all the properties options.
When using this option.
You need to pay attention.
It is based on the flag color option.
Add.
When your style.
Each flag needs to use a separate fabric.
When the button shape or shape size.
This option setting will be very useful.
Now select all properties.
Then press the add and close button at the bottom.
Press the button.
To add the flag color.
In order to be separated from the previous flag color addition.
We changed this file name to all properties.
We can use this flag color mode.
To show the flag color design of the same paper and different materials.
Now let's give this style.
Change the shape of a button.
Adjust the size of the sticker.
If we want to change the direction of the current flag color sticker.
You can choose the sticker in the 3D window.
In the attribute editor on the right side.
Find all flag colors in the link.
After removing the link of the angle.
You can continue to modify the angle of the current sticker.
Under default.
Angle and position are the same.
You can also change the position.
Angle and position are default.
If you remove the link of these two options.
You can freely set and create.
The position and angle of the sticker in each flag color.
Let's take a look at the link option.
This setting can be done without changing its properties.
Copy a flag color scheme.
When you create a flag color.
And some of the fabric of the flag color scheme you choose.
The material of the sticker is completely the same.
You can use this option.
Next, we create a link flag color to demonstrate.
When we click add and close.
We can choose a material in the flag color editor.
The selected material will link yellow highlights.
If we change the color of the sleeve.
You can also change the color.
In addition.
You can open and close all flag colors through the object window.
When you open and show all flag colors.
You can check all the flag color information of the material.
Now we can directly check the flag color information in the object window.
No need to open the flag color editor for inspection.
In the object window.
We can open and close.
Show all flag colors.
When you open this function.
Below each object.
There will be all the flag colors.
We can click the water drop icon in the upper left corner.
To once activate the flag color display of all objects.
You can also click the water drop icon in front of each object.
To display and hide the flag color information of this object.
When you open and show all flag colors.
The color block of the current flag color application.
Will use white border highlight display.
To remind you.
Which flag color are you editing.
First, when you stop the mouse on the color block.
Will appear.
The name of all color matching options used by the object.
For the flag colors added to the material and link mode.
There will be a corresponding color block below each object.
Show the flag color information of the object.
For the flag color of the material type.
You can change the material attribute separately.
For example, texture and color.
The color block only shows the name of this flag color.
If it is the flag color of the link mode.
It will list all the flag color names of the link mode.
If it is the flag color of the all attributes type.
The color block will prompt not used.
As if it is not activated.
Choose this flag color.
If you slide down the wheel in the object window.
You will see.
Through all attributes settings.
Add a color scheme for a single project.
And you will see.
The color block other than the color scheme.
Will be marked as.
Not used.
This is not only suitable for the fabric.
But also suitable for the sticker.
The button.
The eye.
The thread.
And the sewing needle.
Therefore.
You do not need to open the flag color editor.
You can easily check them.
You can also share with you below.
The edit operation in the flag color editor.
Related improvements.
From the object window.
Drag the fabric.
Stickers and accessories and other material documents.
And apply it to the 3D window.
Clothes.
Or on the board.
The material properties.
Will be applied to the object.
All the colors applied.
And for the applied objects.
You can do it for each color.
Set different textures and colors.
Or if you are in the object window.
Drag the project file.
Press the control key on the keyboard.
Then release the left mouse button.
Apply it to the project file.
Then this object will use the link property.
And applied to all flag colors.
Therefore.
When modifying the project later.
Even in one of the flag colors.
Change its properties.
Other properties in the flag color.
Will also be modified at the same time.
If you want to remove the link settings.
Please right-click on the color editor.
In the shrink chart.
And select the material.
Or all properties.
To further edit.
If you want to apply.
A new sticker.
And reset.
All flag colors.
To the link state.
You can press the Shift key on the keyboard.
At the same time.
Select the shrink chart to be modified.
And in the object window.
Drag the applied new sticker file.
To link it.
To the project file.
And to the main page of the project.
This way.
You can change the color of the color.
And then.
You can make the color of the color.
When you are done.
You can click on the color.
And add the color.
From the list.
And the color of the part.
To the next page.
In the next page.
You can see.
The color of the color.
You can change the color.
For example.
If you want to make the color of the flag.
In the lower page.
Open the flag color project file.
In the 2024 version.
Please click on the main menu.
File.
the option of the project file of the 2024.0 version
and save it separately for subsequent use.
This feature update
The functions of QIYISER editor
will become more rich, convenient and efficient.
Welcome to experience